<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Ресурсное планирование"
    id="id-7a06a463b1364c11aa2733128bbb437a"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;A training program is developed and provided to the workforce&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;This service domain administers the development and delivery of a staff training syllabus, including product and service specific training and general skills and management techniques. In some cases where extensive training facilities are provided additional service domains can be defined to administer training plans, booking and training facilities (classroom and media based) operations. Note training needs and certification for an individual employee are maintained in the employee assessment and certification service domains respectively&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Develop and execute a training syllabus covering all general and specific business skills/knowledge requirements and leveraging different training mechanisms and channels as appropriate (classroom, on-line/context based, self taught, desk-side support etc.)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Разработана и предоставлена трудовым ресурсам программа обучения&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Эта область услуг управляет разработкой и реализацией программы обучения персонала, включая обучение конкретным продуктам и услугам, а также общие навыки и методы управления. В некоторых случаях, когда предоставляются широкие возможности для обучения, могут быть определены дополнительные области обслуживания для управления планами обучения, бронирования и обучения (в классе и на основе средств массовой информации). Обратите внимание потребностей в обучении и аттестации для отдельного сотрудника в оценке сотрудника и службы сертификации Домены соответственно&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Разработать и выполнить учебный план, охватывающий все общие и конкретные требования к бизнес-навыкам / знаниям и использующий различные механизмы и каналы обучения (класс, онлайн/контекст, самообучение, поддержка на стороне стола и т. д.)"/>
