<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Document Services"
    id="id-d89a9eb696ca4cb1b7ea897564a00196"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;Legal documents are created, classified and stored for electronic access&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;This service domain handles the status tracking, classification, recording/copying (for all media) storage and retrieval of all active documents. It can include document services that retrieve documents from external sources on request. This can combine physical but more commonly electronic storage, retrieval and distribution of important and/or legally significant documentation. It subscribes to service domain Archive Services for longer term storage needs&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Record, index, classify, scan, store and retrieve any document in any media as appropriate. Includes electronic and physical distribution services&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Юридические документы создаются, классифицируются и хранятся для электронного доступа&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Этот домен обслуживания обрабатывает отслеживание состояния, классификацию, запись / копирование (для всех носителей) хранения и извлечения всех активных документов. Он может включать службы документов, которые извлекают документы из внешних источников по запросу. Это может сочетать физическое, но чаще электронное хранение, поиск и распространение важной и / или юридически значимой документации. Он подписывается на службы архивирования домена службы для долгосрочных потребностей хранения&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Запись, индексирование, классификация, сканирование, хранение и извлечение любого документа на любом носителе. Включает электронные и физические распределительные услуги&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Document Services&#xA;This service domain handles the status tracking, classification, recording/copying (for all media) storage and retrieval of all active documents of significance. It can include document services that retrieve documents from external sources on request. This can combine physical but more commonly electronic storage, retrieval and distribution of important and/or legally significant documentation. It delegates to the service domain Archive Services for longer term storage needs&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain captures, classifies, stores, maintains and retrieves any material document in any media as appropriate. It includes both electronic and physical distribution services&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain captures, classifies, stores, maintains and retrieves any material document in any media as appropriate. It includes both electronic and physical distribution services&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A legal significant document is created during product fulfillment. It is classified and stored for subsequent reference as may be required"/>
