<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Site Administration"
    id="id-0d22b4b10a064fed8a627be8b11157df"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;A business unit moves into a new location requiring that space and equipment be configured and suitable access controls and space assignments made&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;This service domain covers the allocation of space both permanent and temporary to business units and personnel, including the coordination of any office and equipment relocation activity. It also administers the allocation of access passes/rights to individual employees, either as a centralized function or specific to groups of buildings/locations as necessary&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Oversee the configuration and assignment of committed space and facilities to business units to optimize facility leverage and meet business space requirements. Manage the assignment of access rights and security tags etc. to staff as necessary for access control&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Бизнес-подразделение перемещается на новое место, требуя, чтобы пространство и оборудование были настроены и соответствующие средства контроля доступа и назначения пространства&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Эта сфера услуг охватывает предоставление помещений как постоянным, так и временным подразделениям и персоналу, включая координацию любой деятельности по переезду офисных помещений и оборудования. Он также управляет распределением пропусков / прав доступа для отдельных сотрудников, либо в качестве централизованной функции, либо, при необходимости, для групп зданий/мест&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Контроль за конфигурацией и назначением выделенных площадей и помещений подразделениям для оптимизации использования помещений и удовлетворения потребностей в служебных помещениях. Управлять назначением прав доступа и теги безопасности и т. д. персоналу по мере необходимости для контроля доступа&#xA;"/>
