<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Correspondence"
    id="id-97fb9fad4e4242e59414b3114d2bce04"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;A mail shot for an external campaign is developed&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;This service domain handles the (typically) automated generation of batches of pre-formatted correspondence, typically integrating customer/product specific data in correspondence templates for variable aspects of content. Its role could be expanded to handling other aspects of outbound and in-bound correspondence/messaging.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Orchestrate the production of pre-formatted correspondence and batches of correspondence (e.g. mail shots). Optimize delivery bundling and channel selection. Route inbound correspondence&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Разработан почтовый снимок для внешней кампании&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Этот домен обслуживания обрабатывает (обычно) автоматизированное создание пакетов предварительно отформатированной корреспонденции, обычно интегрируя данные о клиенте/продукте в шаблоны корреспонденции для переменных аспектов контента. Его роль может быть расширена для обработки других аспектов исходящей и входящей корреспонденции / обмена сообщениями.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Организация производства предварительно отформатированной корреспонденции и пакетов корреспонденции (например, почтовых снимков). Оптимизируйте связывать поставки и выбор канала. Маршрут входящей корреспонденции&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Correspondence&#xA;This service domain handles the automated generation of batches of pre-formatted correspondence, typically integrating customer/product specific data within correspondence templates. It also handles the tracking of expected responses to sent out mail requests and handles the matching of the response and the onward routing of these and all unsolicited inbound correspondence.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates the production of pre-formatted correspondence and batches of correspondence (e.g. mail shots). It can optimize correspondence 'bundling' and delivery channel/media selection. The service domain can also track for expected responses from correspondence sent to customers and handles the routing of all inbound messages.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates the production of pre-formatted correspondence and batches of correspondence (e.g. mail shots). It can optimize correspondence 'bundling' and delivery channel/media selection. It can also track for expected responses from correspondence sent to customers.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A mail shot is generated for a customer campaign with an identified list of candidate customers and using a standard sales message."/>
