<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Management Manual"
    id="id-f42f698695e3434e8196ea9ec98d9f3b"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;Business management define and promulgate the range of management procedures across the workforce&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;This service domain administers the maintenance and distribution of the organization's Management Manual. This typically covers the general policies, procedures and techniques that need to be followed across the workforce including all health and safety and workforce legal and site and information security related activities. Note additional specialized procedures and techniques will be defined for specialized areas such as risk management and compliance. Also where training and certification is required for procedural compliance, content is part of the management manual but the training and certification is handled by the service domains Workforce Training and Employee Certification&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Develop, maintain and promulgate the management manual of required procedures and guidelines. Provide support in its reference and interpretation as appropriate&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Управление бизнесом определить и обнародовать весь спектр процедур управления персоналом&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Этот домен обслуживает содержание и распределение ручного управления организацией. Это, как правило, охватывает общие политики, процедуры и методы, которые должны соблюдаться в рамках всей рабочей силы, включая все здоровье и безопасность и рабочей силы юридических и сайта и информационной безопасности, связанных с деятельностью. Примечание дополнительные специализированные процедуры и методы будут определены для таких специализированных областей, как управление рисками и соблюдение требований. Также где обучение и сертификация является обязательным для процессуального руководства, содержание часть руководство, но обучение и аттестация осуществляется службой доменов персонала обучение и аттестация работников&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Разработка, ведение и опубликование руководства по управлению требуемыми процедурами и руководящими принципами. Обеспечить поддержку в его ссылке и толковании в зависимости от обстоятельств&#xA;&#xA;"/>
